<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<joblist>
    <job>
        <title>Chiropractor Wanted – Join Our Team in Hawaii</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Waikoloa, HI, USA</location>
        <job_id>796905</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-11-22</date_posted>
        <description>
            We are a patient-centered chiropractic practice located in beautiful Hawaii. Our mission is to holistically care for the spine, extremities, and nervous system using chiropractic adjustments and adjunct therapies tailored to each patient's needs. We foster a collaborative, community-oriented environment where both our Doctors and patients thrive.
            
            We are seeking an enthusiastic and adaptable Chiropractor to join our practice immediately. The role involves providing exceptional chiropractic care to a diverse patient demographic, with an average of 10-20 patients per day, aged 45-60 years. Our clinic combines traditional chiropractic adjustments with adjunct therapies as needed to deliver holistic care. For the right candidate, this can lead to a purchase scenario.
            
            Salary: $90,000-$100,000 base, plus bonuses and incentives.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/hawaii-chiropractor-2</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Experienced Chiropractor Wanted - Signing Bonus</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Spring, TX, USA</location>
        <job_id>847392</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-08-01</date_posted>
        <description>
            Join our state-of-the-art wellness practice located near Spring, Texas. Our open-concept, hands-on chiropractic clinic utilizes diversified, Thompson, and Activator techniques. We prioritize hands-on adjustments as the core of our treatment plans, supplemented with adjunct therapies as needed. Each patient receives an individualized care plan tailored to their specific needs.
            
            We are seeking an expert chiropractor proficient in diversified, Thompson, and Activator techniques, who is passionate about hands-on adjustments. The ideal candidate should excel in working with diverse personalities and firmly believe that adjustments should be the primary treatment approach.
            
            Salary: $87,000 with a competitive signing bonus.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/texas-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Invigorating Chiropractor Opportunity</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Denver, CO, USA</location>
        <job_id>319872</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-07-06</date_posted>
        <description>
            Join our chiropractic clinic nestled in the heart of Denver, Colorado. Our practice is dedicated to personalized patient care and holistic well-being. We seek a passionate chiropractor with exceptional communication skills, empathy, and a commitment to patient-centered care. The ideal candidate will excel in manual adjustments, thrive in a high patient volume setting, and share our mission of promoting holistic wellness through chiropractic care.
            
            Responsibilities include educating patients on body mechanics, physical fitness, exercises, and lifestyle adjustments to foster optimal healing and well-being. Additionally, you will maintain accurate electronic health records and conduct comprehensive patient examinations to identify the root causes of symptoms.
            
            Salary: $85,000 base plus bonuses and incentives.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/colorado-chiropractor-1</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Experienced Chiropractor Needed</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Hilo, HI, USA</location>
        <job_id>726405</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-07-06</date_posted>
        <description>
            Our serene chiropractic oasis is nestled amidst Hawaii's natural beauty, and we invite experienced chiropractors to join our team. Explore the synergy of chiropractic expertise and holistic therapies in our tranquil setting, where we cater to a diverse clientele, blending insurance-covered and private-pay patients seamlessly.
            
            We are seeking a chiropractor to join our harmonious team, where professionalism meets island tranquility. The role encompasses personalized chiropractic care paired with holistic therapies, prioritizing patient needs and fostering community bonds. Candidates with 6-10 years of practice are highly preferred, and there are potential paths towards partnership and ownership.
            
            Salary: $90,000-$100,000 base.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/hawaii-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Holistic Chiropractic Opportunity</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>St. Petersburg, FL, USA</location>
        <job_id>548913</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-07-06</date_posted>
        <description>
            Join our wellness-focused clinic in St. Petersburg, Florida, committed to providing exceptional chiropractic care and promoting holistic well-being. We are looking for a dedicated chiropractor who values patient-centered care and prioritizes holistic health.
            
            Responsibilities include hands-on adjustments, educating patients on posture, ergonomics, exercise, and lifestyle modifications to facilitate optimal healing and well-being, and maintaining accurate electronic health records (EHR).
            
            Salary: $85,000 base plus bonuses and incentives.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/florida-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Exciting Chiropractor Opportunity</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Greenwood Village, CO, USA</location>
        <job_id>745812</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-06-29</date_posted>
        <description>
            Join our patient-centered clinic located in Greenwood Village, Colorado. We are looking for a chiropractor who is passionate about helping patients achieve their health goals and possesses excellent communication skills, empathy, and a patient-centered approach to care. The ideal candidate will be highly experienced in manual adjustments, comfortable with high patient volumes, and committed to promoting holistic well-being through chiropractic care.
            
            Salary: $85,000 base plus bonus and incentives
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/colorado-2-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Wellness-Centric Chiropractor</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Tampa, FL, USA</location>
        <job_id>877346</job_id>
        <date_posted>2024-06-29</date_posted>
        <description>
            Join our patient-centric clinic in Tampa, Florida, dedicated to holistic wellness and exceptional chiropractic care. We are seeking a passionate and skilled manual adjusting chiropractor who prioritizes patient health and well-being.
            
            You will provide exceptional chiropractic care, focusing on optimizing patients' overall health. Responsibilities include education and guidance on posture, ergonomics, exercise, and lifestyle modifications. You will also maintain accurate patient records in electronic health systems.
            
            Salary: $85,000 base plus bonuses and incentives.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/florida-2-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>

    <job>
        <title>Adventurous Chiropractor Opportunity</title>
        <company>Chiropractic Headhunters</company>
        <location>Hanoi, Vietnam</location>
        <job_id>399149</job_id>
        <date_posted>2018-10-05</date_posted>
        <description>
            We are a multi-disciplinary office in Hanoi, Vietnam, seeking an adventurous chiropractor with a strong skillset in diagnosis and the Gonstead or Diversified techniques. This position offers a unique opportunity to work in an international setting while providing high-quality chiropractic care. Full-time position with 28-50 patients per day.
            
            Salary: $5,000 per month plus additional benefits, including Vietnam licensing costs.
        </description>
        <url>https://chiropracticheadhunters.com/vietnam-chiropractor</url>
        <category>Healthcare</category>
        <employment_type>Full-Time</employment_type>
    </job>
</joblist>
